{
    "subject": "resource/CKSW",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1956_establishments_in_Saskatchewan",
    "human_readable": "The subject of CKSW is Category: 1956 establishments in Saskatchewan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9669834971427917,
            "question": "What might have been happening in Saskatchewan during 1956 that led to the establishment of CKSW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7271412014961243,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of another establishment from 1956 in Saskatchewan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6866534948348999,
            "question": "What type of establishment is CKSW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6801679730415344,
            "question": "How has CKSW impacted the community of Saskatchewan since its establishment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5835073590278625,
            "question": "What category does CKSW belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5193948745727539,
            "question": "Is there information available about the founders of CKSW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5117384195327759,
            "question": "In what year was CKSW established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46732550859451294,
            "question": "Where was CKSW established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37161532044410706,
            "question": "Are there any notable events or milestones associated with CKSW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3091016709804535,
            "question": "What is the current status of CKSW today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of CKSW is Category: 1956 establishments in Saskatchewan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2535_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events or milestones associated with CKSW?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2535_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was CKSW established?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2535_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was CKSW established?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2535_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2535_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n**Triple:** The subject of CKSW is Category: 1956 establishments in Saskatchewan.\n\n**Context information analysis:**\n\nThe context information provided includes several documents related to CKSW, a radio station. One of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2535/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt) states that \"CKSW 570 AM (CMR or Country Music Radio) launched in 1956\".\n\nThis information directly supports the triple, indicating that CKSW was established in 1956.\n\nTherefore:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the establishment and history of CKSW Radio, which aired from 1956 in Swift Current, Saskatchewan. This supports that CKSW is a subject related to Category: 1956 establishments in Saskatchewan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}